Captain!
It's an army of monsters!
The stampede's coming!
Aid from the castle didn't
make it in time...
All units!
We will join with the adventurers' guild
and defend our defensive line with our lives!
May the blessing of the spirits
be with the Kingdom of Palettia!
The Magical Revolution
of the Reincarnated Princess and the Genius Young Lady
There they are. Can we get there in time?
I'm worried.
Yeah. I want to get those materials
while they're in good shape.
We gotta hurry!
I'm impressed you seem so
calm about this, Miss Anis.
Yeah, well, this robe is
made of special materials.
Oh, if you're cold, you can stick closer.
No, that's not...
Miss Anis...
Before we leave, there's
something I want to know.
Why do you want the dragon's magicite?
Oh...
So I can be a magician.
What does that have to do with magicite?
I haven't told many people about it...
But using magicite allows you to use a
power that's basically pseudo-magic.
Using it... how?
Oh, well... You need a biological
medium to serve as a catalyst.
A biological medium?
Yeah.
Which is why I had the idea
to implant the magicite in my body.
I've done lots of clinical tests already.
There are no safety issues...
I think.
Your magicology is wonderful.
And your magic tools are
designed to help people.
But any arts performed using
magicite seem frightening to me.
That's fair.
It might just be a way to
turn myself into a monster.
But since I can't use magic the regular way,
it's my only option.
Because that's all I want.
It's started! Let's hurry, Euphie!
Right!
Leader?!
Leave this one to me! Get going!
Help from the capital is never
gonna make it in time.
You gotta survive, even if I don't.
Leader!
Move it! Move it! Move it!
This must be a joke, right?
Hah! I guess only you could get here
from the capital in time!
The plundering princess of the hunt...
The Marauder Princess!
Princess Anisphia?! And Lady Magenta?!
Hey, Captain. Been a while.
So where do we stand?
We've managed to hold the
stampede back thus far.
But the problem is...
The dragon behind it, right?
Okay!
Then you can leave the dragon to me.
I'm basically the only flying
fighter this kingdom has.
Are you serious?!
Rather... Are you sane?!
I am serious, and I'm quite sane.
So while I'm taking care of the dragon,
I want all of you and Euphie
to hold the stampede back.
Very well.
Okay, make it happen!
Miss Anis!
You intend to take on the dragon alone?
Well, it'll be an aerial battle.
I doubt you have any experience with those,
and the stampede's too dangerous
for the knights to stop on their own.
This is just the most effective way.
You understand, don't you, Euphie?
There are some things I can't agree with,
even if I do understand.
Maybe so, but...
I'll be fine.
All right.
Okay, then...
What is that?
A product of my research.
They're pills made with crushed magicite.
I call it "magic medicine."
Magic—
It basically works like
stamina-boosting magic.
It's not what you're thinking.
It does have a few little side effects,
but don't worry.
Those are safe to use, right?!
It's fine! They're legal!
They kinda make you feel hyper
and lose your sense of reason, but...
And how is that "fine"?!
Miss Anis?
I'm fine, really!
Okay, I'm gonna take out some of the
small fry while I wait for the dragon.
Now...
It's time for a super-fun materials hunt!
Die.
Miss Anis!
Grant me now a cage of scorching heat.
Incantation magic...
Envelop everything I see before my eyes,
and reduce it all to embers!
Explosion!
Euphie's magic is so amazing.
So this... is real magic.
That's... the dragon?
It's so...
beautiful!
Amazing! Absolutely amazing!
To think such creatures exist...
The world never ceases to amaze!
Hey, Euphie...
If I had that dragon's magicite,
what do you think I'd be able to do?
Uh...
Okay, I'll be back soon!
Miss Anis...
Nice to meet you.
And now... take this!
Is that...
My blade won't cut it!
What is that thing?!
The Mana Blade—a sword whose
blade is generated by mana—
is my prized invention that cuts through
both physical and magical bodies!
Okay, fine!
What the hell?!
Miss Anis!
Euphie...
Faster... Move faster!
I have to get to her!
Like she did for me!
Miss Anis!
Miss Anis! Are you all right?!
Euphie?
I still have...
You mean to continue fighting?
You almost died just now!
Why would you... go to such lengths for...
It's a simple reason.
Because that's what I feel
a magician should be.
That thing takes people's smiles away.
It can't be allowed to exist.
That's why I fight it.
The ideal magician in my mind
always uses magic to make people smile.
If I run away now, I can't call
myself a magician anymore.
I don't understand.
But if the way you feel is what
allows me to stay here...
I want to protect it.
That's why I don't want to let you go!
I don't want you to die!
If not going now means you
won't be yourself anymore,
then please, at least take me with you!
I won't get in your way!
I want to understand your magic!
If you're worried about the flying,
I've got the hang of it now!
I can assist you! I can defend!
I can be your support!
So... So please...
Don't go alone!
Okay. I won't.
But I do have to stop that thing.
So I have to go.
But you're right. It'll be tough alone.
So I'll ask you myself, Euphie.
Will you come with me?
If that's what you want,
I will accompany you anywhere.
Okay!
Let's go dragon-hunting!
Miss Anis, I believe the dragon has
covered itself with a magic barrier.
A magic barrier...
So that's why!
Thanks, Euphie. Do you know
a way we can get around it?
Would it be too difficult
to get around behind it?
For a body that large to sustain flight,
it must have its own unique magic.
And what's making that possible should be...
Its wings?
Euphie, the only way to get behind that thing
is to shoot straight for it at top speed.
Can you do that?
I can!
I'm putting my life in your hands!
I accepted that long ago.
Our target is its wings.
Wind Cutter!
Now!
Wind Blast!
This time...
You're the one who's gonna fall!
Cut! Cut! Cut! Cut! Cut! Cut! Cut!
Cut it down!
Got it!
Miss Anis!
Nice catch, Euphie!
Miss Anis, we should retreat!
Yeah, that's defini—
We can't.
If we dodge it, that entire area
will be mowed down.
Miss Anis, what are you...
I'm going to cut that thing.
You can't do that! It's impossible!
That thing is magic, too.
And if it's a pure mana shot,
my blade should be able to cut it.
Mana Blade...
Release limiter!
Miss Anis!
If I can't show you that the
impossible can be made possible,
I can't call myself a magician!
All right.
Show me, then. I'll protect you.
I'll be watching!
Just how dense is this mass of mana?
But still, I have to do this!
This is no ordinary sword.
It's my own magic!
It's the infinite potential
that I've envisioned
since the moment I became who I am!
The impossible...
is meant to be made possible!
I-It's over...
Miss Anis?
Well done, visitor.
Do you mean me?
You are victorious.
Do as you please with my corpse.
Um...
I'm sorry. You resent me, don't you?
Resent you?
How truly amusing!
In that case, engrave this
upon your very soul!
My existence, the symbol of my being...
Carry their weight upon your
shoulders for all eternity!
What... is this?
It's like words... or wisdom...
It's been carved into me!
Ah, you who succeeded in slaying me...
May you... May you forever...
bear this curse.
Victory parties are such a drag.
I just can't handle this kind of atmosphere.
Miss Anis?
Oh, Euphie.
I noticed you were nowhere to be found.
So this is where you ran away to.
What about you? Why are you out here?
As a noble, I may be an accomplished dancer,
but in truth, I find contact with men
to be a bit oppressive.
Dance with me, Euphie.
It's not as if you hate dancing, right?
So it's a waste not to.
A waste, is it?
If you hadn't taken me away that day,
I might have cried and cried
until my spirit was broken.
But you took me away from there.
I was so happy.
You gave me a new opportunity
after I'd failed at everything.
Thank you so much for that.
I'm sure you'll do more reckless things in
the future, just like slaying that dragon.
You are someone precious
that I can't let out of my sight.
I hope you will continue to keep me
by your side, Miss Anis.
And I hope you'll always
stay with me, Euphie!
Episode Five
A Magic Medicine and a Magic Sword
Subjugate a Magic Dragon
Episode Six
Getting to the Truth of the
Annulment and the Fascination